{ "_id" : { "$oid" : "53d968259af963e32e6c9b08" }, "order" : 1, "qType" : "text", "placeholder" : "[need placeholder example from team]", "validation" : "^[A-Za-z0-9. -]{1,50}$", "valMsg" : "This answer can be a miximum of 50 characters, and may contain spaces, periods and dashes", "qSet" : "housing-unit", "label" : "Manufacturer name:", "question" : "Who is the manufacturer of your housing unit?", "autocomplete": [ "Adrian Homes","Advanced RV","Airstream","Alaskan Campers","ALP (Adventurer Manufacturing)","American Coach","American Homestar","Americana RV","ATC Recreational Vehicle","Award Recreational Vehicles","B&F Specialties","Beaver","BonnaVilla Homes","Born Free Motorcoach","Breckenridge","Burro Travel Trailers","Cappeart Homes","Cardinal Homes","Casita Travel Trailers","Cavaco Industries","Chalet RV","Champion Homes","Champion Homes of Tennessee","Chariot Eagle","Cheif Industries","Clayton Homes","Coach House","Coachmen","Coleman Camping Trailers","Colony Homes","Columbia Northwest","Commander Homes","Commodore Homes","Cool Amphibious Manufacturers International","Country Coach","Cowboy Cadillac","Crest Homes","CrossRoads Recreational Vehicles","Cruiser RV","Custom Coach","Custom Vehicles","Deer Valley Homes","Design Homes","Destiny Industries","DoubleTree RV","Dutch Housing","Dutchmen Manufacturing","Dynamax","Eagle River Homes","EarthRoamer","Eggcamper","Entegra Coach","Escape Trailer Industries","EverGreen Recreational Vehicles","Excel Homes","Exiss Aluminum Trailers","Extreme Recreational Vehicles","Fairmont Homes","Fleetwood Homes","Fleetwood RV","Forest River RV","Foretravel Motorcoash","Forks RV","Four Wheel Campers","Franklin Homes","Friendship Homes of MN","Fuqua Homes","Fuqua Homes Missouri","General Coach Canada","Giles Industries","Golden West Homes","Great West Vans","GTRV","Gulf Stream Coach","Gulf Stream Trailers","Hallmark Manufacturing","Hallmark Southwest Corp.","Hart Housing Inc.","Haulmark Motorcoaches","Heartland RV","Hemphill Brothers Coach Co.","Highland Manufacturing","Holiday Rambler","Holly Park Homes","Homark Homes","Homebuilders Northwest","Homes by Century","Homes of Merit","Horton Homes","Host Industries","Hy-Line Enterprises","Itasca","Jacobsen Homes","Jayco","K & D Custom Coach","K-Z","KampaRoo Campers","Karsten Homes","Kent Homes","Keystone RV","Kibbi","King Kampers","Kit Homebuilders West","Kottage RV","Lance Camper","Lazy Daze","Leisure Travel Vans","Liberty Coach","Liberty Homes","Little Guy World Wide","Magnolia Homes","Maple Homes Canada","Maple Leaf Homes","Marathon Homes","Marlette Homes","McKenzie RV","Mfg Housing Enterprises","Moduline Homes","Monaco","Monaco Coach Corporation","Nashua Homes","New Castle Homes","New Era Homes","New Horizons","Newell Coach","Newmar","NeXus RV","Northern Lite","Northwood Manufacturing","Nu-Wa","Oak Creek Homes","Oakwood Homes","Open Range","Outdoors RV Manufacturing","Outfitter Manufacturing","Palm Harbor Homes","Palomino RV","Penn Lyon Homes","Peterson Industries","Phoenix Pop Up Truck Campers","Phoenix USA","Pine Grove Homes","Platinum Homes","Pleasure-Way","Powerhouse Coach","Quickup Camper","R-Anell Homes","R-Vision","R.C. Willett Co.","R&R Custom Coach","Recreation by Design","Redwood","Rexhall Industries","Ritz Craft Homes","River Birch homes","Roadtrek","Rochester Homes","S&S Campers","Safari","Scamp Trailers","Schult Homes","Scotbilt Homes","Shadow Lite","Shamrock Homes","Show Hauler Trucks","Silvercrest Homes","Six-Pac Campers","Skyline","Skyline Homes","Solitaire Homes","Southern Energy Homes","Space Craft Manufacturing","Sportsmobile","Starcraft Recreational Vehicles","SunnyBrook","Sunshine Homes","Superior Homes","Taylor Coach","Tentrax","Teton Homes","The Karsten Company","Thor Motor Coach","Tiffin Motorhomes","Titan Homes","Total Result","TrailManor","Travel Lite","Travel Units","Trillium RV","Triple E Recreational Vehicles","Valley Quality Homes","Waverlee Homes ","Weekend Warrior RV","Weis Craft Trailers","West Coast Leisure Homes","Winnebago","Xplorer Motor Homes","Yellowstone RV","Total Result"] }
{ "_id" : { "$oid" : "53d968259af963e32e6c9b09" }, "order" : 2, "qType" : "text", "placeholder" : "[need placeholder example from team]", "validation" : "^[A-Za-z0-9. -]{1,50}$", "valMsg" : "This answer can be a miximum of 50 characters, and may contain spaces, periods and dashes", "qSet" : "housing-unit", "question" : "What model is your housing unit?", "label" : "Model name:", "autocomplete": ["Advanced RV","A. C. E.","Access","Adventurer","Aerbus","Aerolite","Affinity","Airstream","Aliner","Aljo Joey","Allegro","Allegro Breeze","Allegro Bus","Allegro RED","Allure","Alpine","Aluma-Lite","Aluma-Lite A","Aluma-Lite C","Aluma-Lite Ultra","Ambassador","Ameri-Lite","American Eagle","American Heritage","American Revolution","American Tradition","Americana RV","Anthem","Apex","AR-ONE","Arctic Fox","Aspect","Aspen Trail","Aspire","Astoria","ATC RV","Augusta","Autumn Ridge","Avalance","Avanti","Avenue","Award","B Touring Cruiser","Back Country","Baja","Banshee","Basis","Bay Star","Bayridge","Beaver","Berkshire","Big Country","Big Dog","Big Sky Montana","Bighorn","Black Stone","Blackwood","Blue Ridge","Bobcat","Born Free","Bounder","Bounder Diesel","Breckenridge","Bristol Bay","Bronco","Brookside","Brookstone","Bullet","Bunkhouse","Burro","Cambria","Camelot","Canyon Star","Canyon Trail","Capri","Cardinal","Caribou","Cascade","Casita","Catalina","Cayman","Cedar Creek","Centennial","Chalet","Challenger","Champagne Edition","Chaparral","Charleston","Chateau","Cheetah","Cherokee","Citation","Citation Resort","Classic","Classic XT","Clipper","Coachmen","Cobblestone","Coleman","Comet","Compression","Concord","Conquest","Continental Coach","Copper Canyon","CopperLodge","Cornerstone","Cougar","Cougar X-Lite","Country Coach","Country Ridge","Covina","Cowboy Cadillac","Coyote","Creek Side","Crossover","CrossRoads","Cruise Lite","Cruiser","Cuchara","Custom Coach","Cyclone","Cypress","Damara","Daybreak","Denali","Desert Fox","Diplomat","Discover America","Discovery","DRV (was DoubleTree RV)","Dune Chaser","Dune Seeker","Durango","Dutch Star","Dutchmen","Dyna Sport UTV","DynaAire","DynaQuest","Dynasty","DynoMax","Eagle","Eagle Cap","EarthRoamer XV","Eclipse","Eddie Bauer","Edge","Edgewater","Eggcamper","Elegant Lady","Elite","Elite Suites","ElkRidge","Ellipse","Embark","Encounter","Endeavor","Enduramax","Energy","Entegra Coach","Escalade","Escape","Essex","Estate","Ever-Lite","Everest","EverGreen","Excel","Excursion","Executive","Exiss","Expedition","Experience","Explorer","FineLife Cottage","Flagstaff","Fleetwood","Flying Cloud","Forest River","Forester","Foretravel","Four Wheel Campers","Four Winds","Fourwinds","Free Flight","Free Spirit","Freedom Express","Freedom II Libero","Freedom II Serenity","Full House","Fun Finder X","Fun Finder XTRA","Fuzion","Gazelle","Georgetown","Glassic Flat","Grand Junction","Grand Sport","Great West Van","Grey Wolf","Greyhawk","Greystone","GTRV","Guanella","Gulf Breeze","Gulf Coast","GW Van","Hallmark","Hampton","Harmony","Haulmark Motor Garage","Haulmark Motor Home","Haulmark Motorcoaches","Heartland","Hemphill Brothers Coach","Hideout","HitchHiker LS","Holiday Rambler","Hornet","Host","Huron Ridge","Hurricane","Hy-Line","HydePark","Idea","IH","Ikon","Impulse","Inferno","Infinity","Innsbruck","Insignia","Inspire","International","Interstate","Intrigure","Ion","Isata","Itasca","Ivory","Jamboree","Jay Feather","Jay Flight","Jay Series","Journey","Journeyer","Juno","K & D Custom Coach","KampaRoo","King Aire","King Kamper","Kingsport","Knight","Koala","Kodiak","Komfort","Kottage RV","La Veta","Lakewood","Lakota","Lance","Landmark","Lapalma","Laredo","Layton","Lazy Daze","Legend","Leisure Travel","Leprechaun","Lexington","Lexion","Lexor","Liberty Lady Classic","Light","Little Guy","Little Joe","Lodge","Lone Star","LX","Magna","Majestic","Mako","Marathon","Matrix","Maverick","McKenzie","Medallion","Melbourne","Meridian","Mesa Ridge","Milner","Mirada","Mobile Suites","Monaco","Monarch","Montaj","Montana","Montclair","Moriah","MotoMover","Mountain Aire","Mountain View","MPG","MXT","Nash","Navigator","Navion","Nepal","Neptune","New Horizons","Newell","Newmar","NeXus RV","Nimbus","Nomad","North Country","North Trail","Northern Express","Northern Lite","Northstar","Ocean One","Octane ZX","Okanagan","Open Range","Oregon Camper","Outback","Outdoors RV","Outfitter","Outlaw","P-Pod","Palazzo","Palomino","Palomino M-Series","Palomino P-Series","Palomino Ultra-Lite","Palomino Y-Series","Passage","Passport","Pathfinder","Phaeton","Phantom","Phenix","Phoenix","Phoenix Cruiser","Pinnacle","Plateau","Platinum","Pleasure-Way","Ponderosa","Powerhouse Coach","Premier","Prestige","Prevost Conversion","Prism","Prowler","Puma","Queen","Quickup Camper","R&R Custom Coach","Raptor","Raton","Real-Lite","Recon ZX","Recreation by Design","Redwood","Regency","Renegade","Residence","Residential","Retreat","RexAir","Reyo","RidgeLine","Ridgeview","Riptide","RiverStone","Road Warrior","Roadtrek","Roamer","Rock Climber","Rockwood","Rockwood Roo","Rolling Thunder","Roo","Roughneck","Royal","RoyaleCoach","Rubicon","Rushmore","S&S Campers","Sabre","Safari","Salem","Salem Sport","Sandpiper","Sandstorm","Scamp","Scepter","Select Suites","Seneca","Serrano","Shadow Cruiser","Shadow Lite","Shamrock","Shockwave","Show Hauler","Sierra","Siesta","Sightseer","Signature","Silver Creek","Silverado","Simba","Six-Pac","Sky","Skylark","Skyline","SlingShot","Solera","Southwind","Space Craft","Sport","Sport Deck","Sportscoach","Sportsmen","Sportsmobile","Spree","Springdale","Sprinter","Stacker Edge","Stacker RT","Stampede","Starcraft","Starflyer","Starlite","Starwood","Stealth","StoneRidge","Storm","Streamlite","Summerland","Summit","Sun Voyager","Suncruiser","Sundance","SunnyBrook","Sunova","Sunseeker","Sunset Creek","Sunset Trail","Sunstar","SuperNova","Surveyor","Swift","Sydney","Takena","Taylor Coach","Tentrax","Terra","Terra Wind","Teton Homes","Texan","The Alaskan Camper","Timber Ridge","Tioga","Titan","Torrey Pine","Tour","Touring Coach","Track & Trail","Tradition","Trail Runner","Trail-Lite","Trail-Sport","TrailManor","Trailmaster","Trans-Continental","Travel Lite","Travel Star","Travel Units","Traveler","Traverse","Trek","Trillium","Trilogy","Trip","Triple E","True North","Tuscany","Ultimate Suite","Unity","V-Cross","Vacationer","Vantage","Vaulted XT","Ventana","Via","View","Viewfinder","Viking","Viper","Visa","Vista","Vizion","Voltage","Wagoneer","Walkabout","Warrior","WatersEdge","Weekend Warrior","Weekender","West Pointe","Westy","Wildcat","Wilderness","Wildwood","Wildwood Sport","Wind River","Windsor","Windsport","Winnebago","Wolf Pack","Wolf Pup","Work and Play","X-Aire","Xcursion","XLR","Yellowstone","Z-1","Zephyr","Zinger","Total Result"] }
{ "_id" : { "$oid" : "53d968259af963e32e6c9b0a" }, "order" : 3, "qType" : "num", "qSet" : "housing-unit", "question" : "What is your housing unit's year of manufacture?", "validation" : "^(19|20)[0-9]{2}$", "valMsg" : "The year should be 4 digits and represent a year within the last century", "placeholder" : "Format: YYYY", "label" : "Year of manufacture:" }
{ "_id" : { "$oid" : "53d968259af963e32e6c9b0b" }, "order" : 4, "label" : "Select a description", "qType" : "radio", "qSet" : "housing-unit", "question" : "Which of the following describes this housing unit?", "answers" : [ { "text" : "Travel Trailer/Camper" }, { "text" : "Mobile Home" }, { "text" : "Park Model" }, { "text" : "Modular Home" }, { "text" : "Other:" } ], "validation" : "^[A-Za-z0-9. -]{1,30}$", "valMsg" : "This answer can be a miximum of 30 characters, and may contain spaces, periods and dashes", "placeholder" : "Other housing" }
{ "_id" : { "$oid" : "53d968259af963e32e6c9b0c" }, "order" : 5, "qType" : "text", "qSet" : "housing-unit", "question" : "Which city is your housing unit located in?", "label" : "City:", "validation" : "^[A-Za-z0-9. -']{1,30}$", "valMsg" : "This answer can be a miximum of 30 characters, and may contain spaces, periods, apostrophes, and dashes", "placeholder" : "E.g.: New Orleans" }
{ "_id" : { "$oid" : "53d968259af963e32e6c9b0d" }, "order" : 6, "qType" : "text", "qSet" : "housing-unit", "question" : "Which state is your housing unit located in?", "label" : "State:", "validation" : "^[A-Za-z0-9. -']{1,30}$", "valMsg" : "This answer can be a miximum of 30 characters, and may contain spaces, periods, apostrophes, and dashes", "placeholder" : "E.g.: Louisiana" }
{ "_id" : { "$oid" : "53d968279af963e32e6c9b0e" }, "graphType" : "bar", "order" : 9, "label" : "Select one", "qType" : "radio", "qSet" : "symptoms", "question" : "During the last three months, have you experienced fatigue?", "answers" : [ { "text" : "Yes, often (every week)", "nextQ" : 1000 }, { "text" : "Yes, sometimes", "nextQ" : 1000 }, { "text" : "No, never" } ] }
{ "_id" : { "$oid" : "53d968279af963e32e6c9b0f" }, "order" : 1000, "label" : "Select one", "qType" : "radio", "qSet" : "symptoms", "question" : "Do you believe your fatigue is due to your home environment?", "answers" : [ { "text" : "Yes", "nextQ" : 1001 }, { "text" : "No" }, { "text" : "I don't know" } ] }
{ "_id" : { "$oid" : "53d968279af963e32e6c9b10" }, "order" : 1001, "label" : "Select one", "qType" : "radio", "qSet" : "symptoms", "question" : "How much time do you have to spend outside of your home to alleviate your fatigue?", "answers" : [ { "text" : "A few minutes" }, { "text" : "1 hour" }, { "text" : "2 or more hours" }, { "text" : "1 day or more" }, { "text" : "1 week or more" }, { "text" : "this symptom doesn't go away" } ] }
{ "_id" : { "$oid" : "53d968279af963e32e6c9b11" }, "order" : 8, "qType" : "text", "qSet" : "housing-unit", "question" : "What is the zip code for your housing unit's address?", "label" : "Zip code or postal code:", "validation" : "^[A-Za-z0-9 -]{1,10}$", "valMsg" : "This answer can be a miximum of 10 characters, and may contain spaces and dashes", "placeholder" : "70125" }
{ "_id" : { "$oid" : "53d968279af963e32e6c9b12" }, "order" : 7, "qType" : "radio", "qSet" : "housing-unit", "question" : "Which country is your housing unit located in?", "label" : "Country:", "answers" : [ { "text" : "USA" }, { "text" : "Other:" } ], "validation" : "^[A-Za-z0-9. -']{1,30}$", "valMsg" : "This answer can be a miximum of 30 characters, and may contain spaces, periods, apostrophes, and dashes", "placeholder" : "E.g.: Canada" }
{ "_id" : { "$oid" : "53d968679af963e32e6c9b13" }, "order" : 10, "label" : "Select one", "qType" : "radio", "qSet" : "symptoms", "question" : "During the last three months, have you experienced feeling heavy-headed?", "answers" : [ { "text" : "Yes, often (every week)", "nextQ" : 1002 }, { "text" : "Yes, sometimes", "nextQ" : 1002 }, { "text" : "No, never" } ] }
{ "_id" : { "$oid" : "53d968679af963e32e6c9b14" }, "order" : 1002, "label" : "Select one", "qType" : "radio", "qSet" : "symptoms", "question" : "Do you believe your feeling of heavy-headedness is due to your home environment?", "answers" : [ { "text" : "Yes", "nextQ" : 1003 }, { "text" : "No" }, { "text" : "I don't know" } ] }
{ "_id" : { "$oid" : "53d968679af963e32e6c9b15" }, "order" : 1003, "label" : "Select one", "qType" : "radio", "qSet" : "symptoms", "question" : "How much time do you have to spend outside of your home to alleviate your feeling of heavy-headedness?", "answers" : [ { "text" : "A few minutes" }, { "text" : "1 hour" }, { "text" : "2 or more hours" }, { "text" : "1 day or more" }, { "text" : "1 week or more" }, { "text" : "this symptom doesn't go away" } ] }
{ "_id" : { "$oid" : "53d968689af963e32e6c9b16" }, "order" : 11, "label" : "Select one", "qType" : "radio", "qSet" : "symptoms", "question" : "During the last three months, have you experienced memory troubles?", "answers" : [ { "text" : "Yes, often (every week)", "nextQ" : 1004 }, { "text" : "Yes, sometimes", "nextQ" : 1004 }, { "text" : "No, never" } ] }
{ "_id" : { "$oid" : "53d968689af963e32e6c9b17" }, "order" : 1004, "label" : "Select one", "qType" : "radio", "qSet" : "symptoms", "question" : "Do you believe your memory troubles are due to your home environment?", "answers" : [ { "text" : "Yes", "nextQ" : 1005 }, { "text" : "No" }, { "text" : "I don't know" } ] }
{ "_id" : { "$oid" : "53d968689af963e32e6c9b18" }, "order" : 1005, "label" : "Select one", "qType" : "radio", "qSet" : "symptoms", "question" : "How much time do you have to spend outside of your home to alleviate your memory troubles?", "answers" : [ { "text" : "A few minutes" }, { "text" : "1 hour" }, { "text" : "2 or more hours" }, { "text" : "1 day or more" }, { "text" : "1 week or more" }, { "text" : "this symptom doesn't go away" } ] }
{ "_id" : { "$oid" : "53d968699af963e32e6c9b19" }, "order" : 12, "label" : "Select one", "qType" : "radio", "qSet" : "symptoms", "question" : "During the last three months, have you experienced headaches?", "answers" : [ { "text" : "Yes, often (every week)", "nextQ" : 1006 }, { "text" : "Yes, sometimes", "nextQ" : 1006 }, { "text" : "No, never" } ] }
{ "_id" : { "$oid" : "53d968699af963e32e6c9b1a" }, "order" : 1006, "label" : "Select one", "qType" : "radio", "qSet" : "symptoms", "question" : "Do you believe your headaches are due to your home environment?", "answers" : [ { "text" : "Yes", "nextQ" : 1007 }, { "text" : "No" }, { "text" : "I don't know" } ] }
{ "_id" : { "$oid" : "53d968699af963e32e6c9b1b" }, "order" : 1007, "label" : "Select one", "qType" : "radio", "qSet" : "symptoms", "question" : "How much time do you have to spend outside of your home to alleviate your headaches?", "answers" : [ { "text" : "A few minutes" }, { "text" : "1 hour" }, { "text" : "2 or more hours" }, { "text" : "1 day or more" }, { "text" : "1 week or more" }, { "text" : "this symptom doesn't go away" } ] }
{ "_id" : { "$oid" : "53d968699af963e32e6c9b1c" }, "order" : 13, "label" : "Select one", "qType" : "radio", "qSet" : "symptoms", "question" : "During the last three months, have you experienced nausea/dizziness?", "answers" : [ { "text" : "Yes, often (every week)", "nextQ" : 1008 }, { "text" : "Yes, sometimes", "nextQ" : 1008 }, { "text" : "No, never" } ] }
{ "_id" : { "$oid" : "53d968699af963e32e6c9b1d" }, "order" : 1008, "label" : "Select one", "qType" : "radio", "qSet" : "symptoms", "question" : "Do you believe your nausea/dizziness is due to your home environment?", "answers" : [ { "text" : "Yes", "nextQ" : 1009 }, { "text" : "No" }, { "text" : "I don't know" } ] }
{ "_id" : { "$oid" : "53d968699af963e32e6c9b1e" }, "order" : 1009, "label" : "Select one", "qType" : "radio", "qSet" : "symptoms", "question" : "How much time do you have to spend outside of your home to alleviate your nausea/dizziness?", "answers" : [ { "text" : "A few minutes" }, { "text" : "1 hour" }, { "text" : "2 or more hours" }, { "text" : "1 day or more" }, { "text" : "1 week or more" }, { "text" : "this symptom doesn't go away" } ] }
{ "_id" : { "$oid" : "53d9686a9af963e32e6c9b1f" }, "order" : 14, "label" : "Select one", "qType" : "radio", "qSet" : "symptoms", "question" : "During the last three months, have you experienced difficulties concentrating?", "answers" : [ { "text" : "Yes, often (every week)", "nextQ" : 1010 }, { "text" : "Yes, sometimes", "nextQ" : 1010 }, { "text" : "No, never" } ] }
{ "_id" : { "$oid" : "53d9686a9af963e32e6c9b20" }, "order" : 1010, "label" : "Select one", "qType" : "radio", "qSet" : "symptoms", "question" : "Do you believe your difficulties concentrating are due to your home environment?", "answers" : [ { "text" : "Yes", "nextQ" : 1011 }, { "text" : "No" }, { "text" : "I don't know" } ] }
{ "_id" : { "$oid" : "53d9686a9af963e32e6c9b21" }, "order" : 1011, "label" : "Select one", "qType" : "radio", "qSet" : "symptoms", "question" : "How much time do you have to spend outside of your home to alleviate your difficulties concentrating?", "answers" : [ { "text" : "A few minutes" }, { "text" : "1 hour" }, { "text" : "2 or more hours" }, { "text" : "1 day or more" }, { "text" : "1 week or more" }, { "text" : "this symptom doesn't go away" } ] }
{ "_id" : { "$oid" : "53d9686b9af963e32e6c9b22" }, "order" : 15, "label" : "Select one", "qType" : "radio", "qSet" : "symptoms", "question" : "During the last three months, have you experienced itching, burning or irritation of the eyes?", "answers" : [ { "text" : "Yes, often (every week)", "nextQ" : 1012 }, { "text" : "Yes, sometimes", "nextQ" : 1012 }, { "text" : "No, never" } ] }
{ "_id" : { "$oid" : "53d9686b9af963e32e6c9b23" }, "order" : 1012, "label" : "Select one", "qType" : "radio", "qSet" : "symptoms", "question" : "Do you believe that the itching, burning or irritation of your eyes is due to your home environment?", "answers" : [ { "text" : "Yes", "nextQ" : 1013 }, { "text" : "No" }, { "text" : "I don't know" } ] }
{ "_id" : { "$oid" : "53d9686b9af963e32e6c9b24" }, "order" : 1013, "label" : "Select one", "qType" : "radio", "qSet" : "symptoms", "question" : "How much time do you have to spend outside of your home to alleviate itching, burning or irritation of your eyes?", "answers" : [ { "text" : "A few minutes" }, { "text" : "1 hour" }, { "text" : "2 or more hours" }, { "text" : "1 day or more" }, { "text" : "1 week or more" }, { "text" : "this symptom doesn't go away" } ] }
{ "_id" : { "$oid" : "53d9686c9af963e32e6c9b25" }, "order" : 16, "label" : "Select one", "qType" : "radio", "qSet" : "symptoms", "question" : "During the last three months, have you experienced an irritated, stuffy or runny nose?", "answers" : [ { "text" : "Yes, often (every week)", "nextQ" : 1014 }, { "text" : "Yes, sometimes", "nextQ" : 1014 }, { "text" : "No, never" } ] }
{ "_id" : { "$oid" : "53d9686c9af963e32e6c9b26" }, "order" : 1014, "label" : "Select one", "qType" : "radio", "qSet" : "symptoms", "question" : "Do you believe your irritated, stuffy or runny nose is due to your home environment?", "answers" : [ { "text" : "Yes", "nextQ" : 1015 }, { "text" : "No" }, { "text" : "I don't know" } ] }
{ "_id" : { "$oid" : "53d9686c9af963e32e6c9b27" }, "order" : 1015, "label" : "Select one", "qType" : "radio", "qSet" : "symptoms", "question" : "How much time do you have to spend outside of your home to alleviate your irritated, stuffy or runny nose?", "answers" : [ { "text" : "A few minutes" }, { "text" : "1 hour" }, { "text" : "2 or more hours" }, { "text" : "1 day or more" }, { "text" : "1 week or more" }, { "text" : "this symptom doesn't go away" } ] }
{ "_id" : { "$oid" : "53d9686c9af963e32e6c9b28" }, "order" : 17, "label" : "Select one", "qType" : "radio", "qSet" : "symptoms", "question" : "During the last three months, have you experienced a hoarse, dry throat?", "answers" : [ { "text" : "Yes, often (every week)", "nextQ" : 1016 }, { "text" : "Yes, sometimes", "nextQ" : 1016 }, { "text" : "No, never" } ] }
{ "_id" : { "$oid" : "53d9686c9af963e32e6c9b29" }, "order" : 1016, "label" : "Select one", "qType" : "radio", "qSet" : "symptoms", "question" : "Do you believe your hoarse, dry throat is due to your home environment?", "answers" : [ { "text" : "Yes", "nextQ" : 1017 }, { "text" : "No" }, { "text" : "I don't know" } ] }
{ "_id" : { "$oid" : "53d9686c9af963e32e6c9b2a" }, "order" : 1017, "label" : "Select one", "qType" : "radio", "qSet" : "symptoms", "question" : "How much time do you have to spend outside of your home to alleviate your hoarse, dry throat?", "answers" : [ { "text" : "A few minutes" }, { "text" : "1 hour" }, { "text" : "2 or more hours" }, { "text" : "1 day or more" }, { "text" : "1 week or more" }, { "text" : "this symptom doesn't go away" } ] }
{ "_id" : { "$oid" : "53d9686d9af963e32e6c9b2b" }, "order" : 18, "label" : "Select one", "qType" : "radio", "qSet" : "symptoms", "question" : "During the last three months, have you experienced a cough?", "answers" : [ { "text" : "Yes, often (every week)", "nextQ" : 1018 }, { "text" : "Yes, sometimes", "nextQ" : 1018 }, { "text" : "No, never" } ] }
{ "_id" : { "$oid" : "53d9686d9af963e32e6c9b2c" }, "order" : 1018, "label" : "Select one", "qType" : "radio", "qSet" : "symptoms", "question" : "Do you believe your cough is due to your home environment?", "answers" : [ { "text" : "Yes", "nextQ" : 1019 }, { "text" : "No" }, { "text" : "I don't know" } ] }
{ "_id" : { "$oid" : "53d9686d9af963e32e6c9b2d" }, "order" : 1019, "label" : "Select one", "qType" : "radio", "qSet" : "symptoms", "question" : "How much time do you have to spend outside of your home to alleviate your cough?", "answers" : [ { "text" : "A few minutes" }, { "text" : "1 hour" }, { "text" : "2 or more hours" }, { "text" : "1 day or more" }, { "text" : "1 week or more" }, { "text" : "this symptom doesn't go away" } ] }
{ "_id" : { "$oid" : "53d9686e9af963e32e6c9b2e" }, "order" : 19, "label" : "Select one", "qType" : "radio", "qSet" : "symptoms", "question" : "During the last three months, have you experienced any asthma attacks?", "answers" : [ { "text" : "Yes, often (every week)", "nextQ" : 1020 }, { "text" : "Yes, sometimes", "nextQ" : 1020 }, { "text" : "No, never" } ] }
{ "_id" : { "$oid" : "53d9686e9af963e32e6c9b2f" }, "order" : 1020, "label" : "Select one", "qType" : "radio", "qSet" : "symptoms", "question" : "Do you believe your asthma attacks are due to your home environment?", "answers" : [ { "text" : "Yes", "nextQ" : 1021 }, { "text" : "No" }, { "text" : "I don't know" } ] }
{ "_id" : { "$oid" : "53d9686e9af963e32e6c9b30" }, "order" : 1021, "label" : "Select one", "qType" : "radio", "qSet" : "symptoms", "question" : "How much time do you have to spend outside of your home to alleviate your asthma attacks?", "answers" : [ { "text" : "A few minutes" }, { "text" : "1 hour" }, { "text" : "2 or more hours" }, { "text" : "1 day or more" }, { "text" : "1 week or more" }, { "text" : "this symptom doesn't go away" } ] }
{ "_id" : { "$oid" : "53d9686e9af963e32e6c9b31" }, "order" : 20, "label" : "Select one", "qType" : "radio", "qSet" : "symptoms", "question" : "During the last three months, have you experienced any nose bleeds?", "answers" : [ { "text" : "Yes, often (every week)", "nextQ" : 1022 }, { "text" : "Yes, sometimes", "nextQ" : 1022 }, { "text" : "No, never" } ] }
{ "_id" : { "$oid" : "53d9686e9af963e32e6c9b32" }, "order" : 1022, "label" : "Select one", "qType" : "radio", "qSet" : "symptoms", "question" : "Do you believe your nose bleeds are due to your home environment?", "answers" : [ { "text" : "Yes", "nextQ" : 1023 }, { "text" : "No" }, { "text" : "I don't know" } ] }
{ "_id" : { "$oid" : "53d9686e9af963e32e6c9b33" }, "order" : 1023, "label" : "Select one", "qType" : "radio", "qSet" : "symptoms", "question" : "How much time do you have to spend outside of your home to alleviate your nose bleeds?", "answers" : [ { "text" : "A few minutes" }, { "text" : "1 hour" }, { "text" : "2 or more hours" }, { "text" : "1 day or more" }, { "text" : "1 week or more" }, { "text" : "this symptom doesn't go away" } ] }
{ "_id" : { "$oid" : "53d9686f9af963e32e6c9b34" }, "order" : 21, "label" : "Select one", "qType" : "radio", "qSet" : "symptoms", "question" : "During the last three months, have you experienced dry or flushed facial skin?", "answers" : [ { "text" : "Yes, often (every week)", "nextQ" : 1024 }, { "text" : "Yes, sometimes", "nextQ" : 1024 }, { "text" : "No, never" } ] }
{ "_id" : { "$oid" : "53d9686f9af963e32e6c9b35" }, "order" : 1024, "label" : "Select one", "qType" : "radio", "qSet" : "symptoms", "question" : "Do you believe your dry or flushed facial skin is due to your home environment?", "answers" : [ { "text" : "Yes", "nextQ" : 1025 }, { "text" : "No" }, { "text" : "I don't know" } ] }
{ "_id" : { "$oid" : "53d9686f9af963e32e6c9b36" }, "order" : 1025, "label" : "Select one", "qType" : "radio", "qSet" : "symptoms", "question" : "How much time do you have to spend outside of your home to alleviate your dry or flushed facial skin?", "answers" : [ { "text" : "A few minutes" }, { "text" : "1 hour" }, { "text" : "2 or more hours" }, { "text" : "1 day or more" }, { "text" : "1 week or more" }, { "text" : "this symptom doesn't go away" } ] }
{ "_id" : { "$oid" : "53d968709af963e32e6c9b37" }, "order" : 22, "label" : "Select one", "qType" : "radio", "qSet" : "symptoms", "question" : "During the last three months, have you experienced scaling/itching scalp or ears?", "answers" : [ { "text" : "Yes, often (every week)", "nextQ" : 1026 }, { "text" : "Yes, sometimes", "nextQ" : 1026 }, { "text" : "No, never" } ] }
{ "_id" : { "$oid" : "53d968709af963e32e6c9b38" }, "order" : 1026, "label" : "Select one", "qType" : "radio", "qSet" : "symptoms", "question" : "Do you believe your scaling/itching scalp or ears is due to your home environment?", "answers" : [ { "text" : "Yes", "nextQ" : 1027 }, { "text" : "No" }, { "text" : "I don't know" } ] }
{ "_id" : { "$oid" : "53d968709af963e32e6c9b39" }, "order" : 1027, "label" : "Select one", "qType" : "radio", "qSet" : "symptoms", "question" : "How much time do you have to spend outside of your home to alleviate your scaling/itching scalp or ears?", "answers" : [ { "text" : "A few minutes" }, { "text" : "1 hour" }, { "text" : "2 or more hours" }, { "text" : "1 day or more" }, { "text" : "1 week or more" }, { "text" : "this symptom doesn't go away" } ] }
{ "_id" : { "$oid" : "53d968719af963e32e6c9b3a" }, "order" : 23, "label" : "Select one", "qType" : "radio", "qSet" : "symptoms", "question" : "During the last three months, have you experienced hands with dry, itching, or red skin?", "answers" : [ { "text" : "Yes, often (every week)", "nextQ" : 1028 }, { "text" : "Yes, sometimes", "nextQ" : 1028 }, { "text" : "No, never" } ] }
{ "_id" : { "$oid" : "53d968719af963e32e6c9b3b" }, "order" : 1028, "label" : "Select one", "qType" : "radio", "qSet" : "symptoms", "question" : "Do you believe your hands with dry, itching, or red skin is due to your home environment?", "answers" : [ { "text" : "Yes", "nextQ" : 1029 }, { "text" : "No" }, { "text" : "I don't know" } ] }
{ "_id" : { "$oid" : "53d968719af963e32e6c9b3c" }, "order" : 1029, "label" : "Select one", "qType" : "radio", "qSet" : "symptoms", "question" : "How much time do you have to spend outside of your home to alleviate your hands with dry, itching, or red skin?", "answers" : [ { "text" : "A few minutes" }, { "text" : "1 hour" }, { "text" : "2 or more hours" }, { "text" : "1 day or more" }, { "text" : "1 week or more" }, { "text" : "this symptom doesn't go away" } ] }
{ "_id" : { "$oid" : "53d968719af963e32e6c9b3d" }, "order" : 24, "label" : "Select one", "qType" : "radio", "qSet" : "symptoms", "question" : "During the last three months, have you experienced changes in sense of smell or taste?", "answers" : [ { "text" : "Yes, often (every week)", "nextQ" : 1030 }, { "text" : "Yes, sometimes", "nextQ" : 1030 }, { "text" : "No, never" } ] }
{ "_id" : { "$oid" : "53d968719af963e32e6c9b3e" }, "order" : 1030, "label" : "Select one", "qType" : "radio", "qSet" : "symptoms", "question" : "Do you believe your changes in sense of smell or taste is due to your home environment?", "answers" : [ { "text" : "Yes", "nextQ" : 1031 }, { "text" : "No" }, { "text" : "I don't know" } ] }
{ "_id" : { "$oid" : "53d968719af963e32e6c9b3f" }, "order" : 1031, "label" : "Select one", "qType" : "radio", "qSet" : "symptoms", "question" : "How much time do you have to spend outside of your home to alleviate your changes in sense of smell or taste?", "answers" : [ { "text" : "A few minutes" }, { "text" : "1 hour" }, { "text" : "2 or more hours" }, { "text" : "1 day or more" }, { "text" : "1 week or more" }, { "text" : "this symptom doesn't go away" } ] }
{ "_id" : { "$oid" : "53d968729af963e32e6c9b40" }, "order" : 25, "label" : "Select one", "qType" : "radio", "qSet" : "symptoms", "question" : "During the last three months, have you experienced nightmares?", "answers" : [ { "text" : "Yes, often (every week)", "nextQ" : 1038 }, { "text" : "Yes, sometimes", "nextQ" : 1038 }, { "text" : "No, never" } ] }
{ "_id" : { "$oid" : "53d968729af963e32e6c9b41" }, "order" : 1038, "label" : "Select one", "qType" : "radio", "qSet" : "symptoms", "question" : "Do you believe your nightmares are due to your home environment?", "answers" : [ { "text" : "Yes", "nextQ" : 1039 }, { "text" : "No" }, { "text" : "I don't know" } ] }
{ "_id" : { "$oid" : "53d968729af963e32e6c9b42" }, "order" : 1039, "label" : "Select one", "qType" : "radio", "qSet" : "symptoms", "question" : "How much time do you have to spend outside of your home to alleviate your nightmares?", "answers" : [ { "text" : "A few minutes" }, { "text" : "1 hour" }, { "text" : "2 or more hours" }, { "text" : "1 day or more" }, { "text" : "1 week or more" }, { "text" : "this symptom doesn't go away" } ] }
{ "_id" : { "$oid" : "53d968969af963e32e6c9b43" }, "order" : 26, "label" : "Select one", "qType" : "radio", "qSet" : "symptoms", "question" : "During the last three months, have you experienced insomnia?", "answers" : [ { "text" : "Yes, often (every week)", "nextQ" : 1036 }, { "text" : "Yes, sometimes", "nextQ" : 1036 }, { "text" : "No, never" } ] }
{ "_id" : { "$oid" : "53d968969af963e32e6c9b44" }, "order" : 1036, "label" : "Select one", "qType" : "radio", "qSet" : "symptoms", "question" : "Do you believe your insomnia is due to your home environment?", "answers" : [ { "text" : "Yes", "nextQ" : 1037 }, { "text" : "No" }, { "text" : "I don't know" } ] }
{ "_id" : { "$oid" : "53d968969af963e32e6c9b45" }, "order" : 1037, "label" : "Select one", "qType" : "radio", "qSet" : "symptoms", "question" : "How much time do you have to spend outside of your home to alleviate your insomnia?", "answers" : [ { "text" : "A few minutes" }, { "text" : "1 hour" }, { "text" : "2 or more hours" }, { "text" : "1 day or more" }, { "text" : "1 week or more" }, { "text" : "this symptom doesn't go away" } ] }
{ "_id" : { "$oid" : "53d968969af963e32e6c9b46" }, "order" : 27, "label" : "Select one", "qType" : "radio", "qSet" : "symptoms", "question" : "During the last three months, have you experienced diarrhea?", "answers" : [ { "text" : "Yes, often (every week)", "nextQ" : 1034 }, { "text" : "Yes, sometimes", "nextQ" : 1034 }, { "text" : "No, never" } ] }
{ "_id" : { "$oid" : "53d968969af963e32e6c9b47" }, "order" : 1034, "label" : "Select one", "qType" : "radio", "qSet" : "symptoms", "question" : "Do you believe your diarrhea is due to your home environment?", "answers" : [ { "text" : "Yes", "nextQ" : 1035 }, { "text" : "No" }, { "text" : "I don't know" } ] }
{ "_id" : { "$oid" : "53d968969af963e32e6c9b48" }, "order" : 1035, "label" : "Select one", "qType" : "radio", "qSet" : "symptoms", "question" : "How much time do you have to spend outside of your home to alleviate your diarrhea?", "answers" : [ { "text" : "A few minutes" }, { "text" : "1 hour" }, { "text" : "2 or more hours" }, { "text" : "1 day or more" }, { "text" : "1 week or more" }, { "text" : "this symptom doesn't go away" } ] }
{ "_id" : { "$oid" : "53da7a8e5d59643ea6902be0" }, "order" : 28, "label" : "Select a description", "qType" : "radio", "qSet" : "symptoms", "question" : "How would you rate your health currently?", "answers" : [ { "text" : "Excellent" }, { "text" : "Very Good" }, { "text" : "Good" }, { "text" : "Fair" }, { "text" : "Poor" } ] }
{ "_id" : { "$oid" : "53da7a8e5d59643ea6902be1" }, "order" : 29, "label" : "Select a description", "qType" : "radio", "qSet" : "symptoms", "question" : "How would you rate your health before living in this housing unit?", "answers" : [ { "text" : "Excellent" }, { "text" : "Very Good" }, { "text" : "Good" }, { "text" : "Fair" }, { "text" : "Poor" } ] }
{ "_id" : { "$oid" : "53da7a8e5d59643ea6902be2" }, "order" : 30, "label" : "Select a description", "qType" : "radio", "qSet" : "symptoms", "question" : "Do you feel healthier in general when you spend less time in the trailer?", "answers" : [ { "text" : "Yes" }, { "text" : "No" }, { "text" : "Don't know" } ] }
